{"data":[{"question":"Students in the United States often support themselves by babysitting, working in restaurants, or ________ taxicabs.","a":"they drive","b":"to drive","c":"driving","d":"drive","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Driving: follow a series of gerund ( babysitting, working in).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"She viewed the ________ of a week alone in the house without much enthusiasm.","a":"prospect","b":"prospects","c":"prospector","d":"prospective","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The + noun.\u00a0\n- Prospect: someone who looks for gold, minerals, oil.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Those of us who have a family history of heart disease should make yearly appointments with ________ doctors.","a":"their","b":"our","c":"his","d":"her","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Our is possessive pronoun of \"we\".\u00a0\n- Those of us- our.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Although federal support for basic research programs ________ much less than it was ten years ago, more funds are now available from the national science foundation.","a":"are","b":"is","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tense agreement: When the main clause is in past tense, if the subordinate clause the which shows an action occurring at the same time will be simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject ( federal support ) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Located in New York, apartments cost more to rent than they ________ In other, smaller cities.","a":"do","b":"did","c":"will","d":"would","answer":"1","explain":"\n-Things to compare must be equal- person-person; object-object, verb to verb... \n- Do: auxiliary of the present simple tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"This new model not only saves time but also ________ by operating on two batteries instead of four.","a":"energy","b":"to save energy","c":"save energy","d":"saves energy","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Not only...but also...: things mentioned in ...must be equal (form, structure...).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The government requires that a census be taken every ten years ________ accurate statistics may be compiled.","a":"so","b":"so that","c":"such","d":"such that","answer":"2","explain":"\n- So that + clause: in order to make something happen, make something possible.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"The main ________ of economics success is our ability to control inflation.","a":"determinant","b":"determination","c":"determine","d":"determined","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The + noun.\u00a0\n- Determinant: something that strongly influences what you do or how you behave.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is responsible ________ the project?","a":"for","b":"to","c":"with","d":"about","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be responsible for.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"},{"question":"Television has little ________ for me.","a":"attract","b":"attractive","c":"attraction","d":"attractively","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Have + noun\/noun phrase (adj + noun).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"9","type":"1"}]}